Welcome back everybody to the entire Extreme Masters live from Taipei. We are here at the Taipei
Games show at the Taipei World Trade Center. Hope you've enjoyed your morning or evening
so far. We've got a couple of good games left to come and the second semi-finals, of course,
first before the grand finals and it's time for the rematch of the Inter Extreme Masters World
Championship from 2014. A big big game coming up, joining me on the desk, of course, is the three
guys that are here earlier this morning as Pig, Todd and Claris. A good start to the day, some very
high skilled Starcraft 2 to start things off James. Yeah, some really cool stuff. Trive in
Sokey crazy poor guy and we're having to deal with all of that aggression but you're never let up.
So it's really nice to see like a Terran really drive home that kind of aggression and not slip
up back home as well, always having more and more coming to a nice Sokey. Yeah, and it's a great
thing to see. You'll make it to the finals and we saw that emotion, you talked about it in the cast
and he's very happy to be there. Oh yeah, I mean it's something everyone's been looking forward
to seeing the unplay and I think I was one of the few cynics. I was kind of like coming into this
tournament. I'm like is he just going to get here and just like you know he's just going to like
nervous on the stage and just going to fall apart and he's delivered so far. 3-0, now 3-1
going into the finals and you can see on his face the elation, he's kind of building up that
momentum so I think whoever goes up against him in the finals they got a really hard shot.
And he's got a full backing of the community as well we're happy to see him play but Todd,
you're a pro to us player. We know that and we have a PvP coming up and it is a very high level PvP
coming of course the rematch of the world championship back in 2014.
Who? Absolutely yeah I mean these two have history but now it's legacy of the void you start with
a lot more more probes than you used to and Proxy is not going to be nearly as easy then again it's SOS
you know like if there is if there are crazy builds to be used in there he's going to be the one
to try and use some of these you know maps like the towers of those shipyards you can wall of your ramp
and then your opponents not going to know whether you're getting Stargate or DT's which for both of
these tech it's very different on how you counter it and we already saw this kind of build early
on the tournament when SOS played against MC and he won 3-0 you some dTs that surprise MC did a
lot of damage force him to all in then which then was held so hero is gonna have to be on his A game
here he's gonna have to scout a lot he's gonna have to try and realize what's happening because if
he's not able to do that he's going up against a guy who I feel like we should qualify of
math and mathematicians slash mad scientists he does his calculations before his matches and he
seems like he almost always gets it right I was watching him earlier actually over there in the
warmer area and he was just watching Vioides and sometimes he will pose and I think he was watching
I think he was like dear I can somebody in a Korean league and he would just pose sometimes and
think for a little bit he'd be like yeah he's like you did it good but it could be this this and this
pilot but the doctorine equals 15 dead probes and like we'll do that and then he would resume the
replay and be like yeah I mean these guys are pretty bad but maybe I can improve this build myself
and use it later and better and so that's the exciting thing about SOS and hopefully this PvP series
as well that it is gonna be a chaos okay it is gonna be entertaining but I think if we take a step
back and look at both of the players they haven't had the best of starting like it's the void if you
think back to how well they performed in the other swarm of course SOS the reigning world champion
and legacy the void though they've tripped up a couple of times in some of the tournaments in
Korea already especially in PvP you look at both players and they've had a really hard time
hero had two recent losses in PvP and even though there were one two losses some of the mistakes
he was making in those games he did not confident and there's a difference between losing a game where
things don't quite work out in terms of your build order and how the strategies go but he really
looked like he was lacking confidence in the match up so some of those matches were only about a
week two weeks ago he's gonna have to have really kind of improve that confidence from there
and SOS also had quite a one-sided defeat one three to deer himself not long ago you have a good
point but keep in mind though this is the Intel Extreme Masters not some minor tournament boys
and I think also in Korea like a lot with the restart of Starcraft 2 it being going from
our hardest ones legacy of the void a lot of the Koreans that weren't necessarily getting the top
results in the previous iteration of the game and now really really hungry to actually take those
top spots they've been working their absolute passes off to try and actually get those wins and
they've been able to topple people like hero and SOS and in protestors this is pro oh well
this is kind of a silly way to open the statement up but in Starcraft 2 then it's a better way to say
this in a best of five you can obviously study free opponent and we've having a lot of PvP games
been played recently both of them now can approach this they've obviously had 24 hours knowing who
they go and up against or maybe you know more than that if they thought they were gonna win the
tournament said okay let me look at the bracket I'm gonna be you then I'm gonna probably play you
what type of preparation could we be seeing here from both of these players I mean heroes known
for that likewise SOS yeah there is just so much to take in consideration not just the history
between these two the fact that they've played a lot in another expansion in the past but also
the recent histories against different opponents in the matchup where we had SOS yesterday
take on MC beat him 3 0 he showed some of his builds and usually when SOS plays in a tournament like
this or like any player you look at the series and you're like okay well I guess he was just one of
the series where everything went right for him but SOS is that tournament like for example the MS
size master gaming arena last year where every single one of his series was like a Cinderella story of
like great things happening to him everything was going his way no matter what he was doing he was
beating innovation to 0 3 0 solar later like he was just unstoppable so hero here he's basically
gonna have to maybe like roll the dice here and there and at the same time try to play decently
like our pretty solids and hope to not get unfortunate in certain spots because there is no way in
ppp that you can see everything that you can scout everything so sometimes you have to take risks
but he's gonna need to try and minimize them but not that much that if he gets it wrong he's in a
really bad position if that makes sense I'm trying to follow you actually the rolling dice to take
him risks to keeping that at a minimal but he's going up against SOS doesn't that complicate things
though I mean if you look at a normal protest maybe that is the correct approach but SOS is such a
different player absolutely and I feel like maybe less so in legacy of the void even though like I
say we've seen builds you know like some proxies or even like just the fact that you can wall off
your ramp and that you open and won't be able to know in any way what you're doing it's just so
crazy like if I had to play SOS and like he did this every single game I would just be like okay I
guess like a forfeit like what am I supposed to do like it's so difficult to properly counter like
everything if you know what you're doing doing and SOS knows how to use that to his trends so that's
what could make it very difficult for here the maps are gonna be very important clearly here yeah
like full play maps two play maps yeah starting I mentioned dust towers and orbital shipyards being
two maps that can be very tricky because like you got an easy expansion that you can take and you can
wall off the ramp and then hide your take and then you have a very small slash aggressive map in
all rena where you can three pile on rush yeah open on those anything a little bit different and the
standard double gate stalker so again like lots of possibilities here and of course here is SOS he's
just now got into the booth on stage and he's ready to play just about ready to play but he took a win
seemingly easy so win against MC30 but surely that's also a bit of a weakness having played MC shown
PVP show and what is capable of yeah see what you see when you actually have that is a bit annoying
here for him but again going up against hero I almost always give SOS the mental edge when it comes
to playing against hero he has beaten him high octane pressure situations and if my money's
anything to bet on I think he'll probably end up doing it again this is going to be difficult
fair I think there is there is actually many ways to look at this you know you could be like oh yeah
he played MCs already revealed how he pays against protesters but he's reeled MC that's impressive
in yourself yeah and like the haters out there are probably like yeah you know MCs are streaming now
no no no no no like shut up in the worst of auto he's shut up don't even go there like MCs a fantastic
player he made top 16 player master recently that was a huge already series out of SOS all right
so final thoughts and boys predictions and then I want to get someone out of pig because he has
been a little bit quite a very close to start with you their predictions as much as I love hero
I think SOS just always has his number and I think three one once again two SOS
Johan Murlow I thought the look on heroes face after he lost in a hundred thousand dollars fine
round finals winner takes all and I'm pretty sure he wants this revenge more badly than
probably anything right now so I think he's he has he has the desire here to win he's going to win it
three two okay and pick prediction and final thoughts here yeah I think we've got three one
for for SOS actually I think there's just that mental edge and you can see hero on screen he's trying
to actually gather his thoughts gather his focus because he knows he's going to need every little bit
and SOS historically has always thrived in the messy situations you're sure you can go into
the game with an opening but once you get there here is the player who isn't quite as decisive as
SOS when it comes to figuring out what's the next weird step to throw my opponent off so I think
here is really good at going here and he's got to find a way to thrive in the chaos and stay confident
all right thank you very much pig it's time to head over to the concrete team for this one
it's none other then Todd and Kalaris because who else would it be here for a PVP as we have two
worlds colliding only on the cast is this but also in game hero versus SOS orbital shipyard will be
our first map to start things off and this is going to be a rip roaring adventure Todd because one
of these is going on to the grand final absolutely I talked a little bit about how this map can be tricky
if SOS in particular where to try and go for some sort of wall of trying hidey stack as much as he
can hero though how is he going to approach this does he try and play something a little bit
riskier which maybe will be unexpected by SOS or does he try to still place usual safer style
where he's the one scouting trying to realize what is up against and then counter it properly or I
guess we'll find out here in a second and getting the momentum going as well in PVP is going to be
very important here yeah opening with a map win in this kind of series can decide a lot I mean a lot
of PVP before revolved around the idea of the bling stalkers and disruptors being case but we see
a lot of star gay openness now really kind of in the mix and causing a lot of hecticness in the star
I'm glad you mentioned that actually because it really feels like if a PVP is a slow one so usually
like worst players than the world's absolute best you're gonna see disruptors in action a lot of
the time because like you need to you need to get those you know from a certain point in game when
you have three bases when you already have bling and stuff is nothing's happening you need to add
disruptors because if you don't you're not going to be able to win the fight ever and a lot of the
time to win in stock if you need to actually win the fight against the opponent's army but
players have gotten so good these days and everybody plays so aggressive that we see less and
less disruptors we see a lot of bling stalkers some emotals some attacks the thing is though on the
map like this it's actually very hard to properly go across the map and to crippling damage or
succeed with any big attacks but I guess these guys are just so good with the bling stalkers and
all of this that we could definitely see some very action packed game the series is definitely
gonna be longer than the one day they played in the world championship in Katowice though I can
promise you that yeah just a little bit one with suspect here as that was all about them proxies
not as easy to get away with something like they here now in legacy of the void but I mean even
still I can't there they can be like dark shrine and tell twilight council pop sees onto the middle
of the map to try and catch someone off guard early on there's days there's a chance as to as
maybe it was like a crazy proxy with like a couple gateways yeah but I feel like it's unlikely it's
really not that great it's been figured out for the most part same as for a cannon rush
cannon rush we don't really see almost ever maybe on the arena but no other days I feel like
everybody except me knows how to counter so you probably would be a good idea
uh bad idea right go for something like this like somebody a hero if ss wanted to try but then
again it's ss we're talking about even remember his pvc in hard and smart he will literally know all
the absolute best places on every single map on where to cannon rush yeah so maybe in pvp here you
can find a few spots where he can do something like that but like I said it's it's very tricky to
get any of those to work here okay well it seems though we have had a drop into this first game so
we're gonna have to get this re hosted by the looks of things mr. yesl ob3 whoever you are
get it to get it together man what's it going on I thought it was me for a second no no no no not you
not you by the looks of things um i'm not even sure why i am on this one i guess i'm number two
but yeah well we're getting back into this in just a moment but we've we've spoken about it we know
that these guys have a lot of history against one another for me i always pick ss going into it i
just can't get away from the idea that he has such a good position against his opponent in hero
and i i like the point that you know Sean made at the desk they haven't had the most amazing
of starts here to that legacy of the void kind of uh resurgence once the game changes from heart
this form to legacy i really wonder actually in terms of build orders here what s ss ss has decided
to pick because like he's approached to the matchup you know we've kind of narrowed it down to
his like this crazy guy who does his his mathematics his calculations and then decides to build
that he thinks he's gonna give the biggest give him the biggest edge but like i said like it's very
easy to get it wrong and if you get it wrong even just one single time you can lose momentum let
you open gain the confidence he needs to start playing better and then from there only goes downhill
and you can't let somebody like hero you know gain momentum in a series like this so ss
his calculations here they're gonna have to be correct man yeah for sure this is uh gonna be
very very important between these two i think overall depending on who goes forwards i really can't
attribute to who would even do better against Bjorn i mean both of them have got you know
really good chances of course they're they're very very strong powerhouse protest but Bjorn is like
in this weird world where i mean the storm in the desk and he looked pretty darn confident and
kind of relaxed almost when you guys were talking to him yeah um it's almost as if you know he's been
waiting for this for a long time and now that it's here he's like not even surprised you know he's
worked very hard for this which you know for a lot of programmers he makes a lot of sense but uh he
would go up against two of the or one in this case of the absolute best protests in the world in the
history of starcraft too in either ss or hero that'd be a pretty big task to take on
i have to show him all right well uh we are maybe just waiting for one more observer but
let's say we are good to go without ob-3 causing off problems ob-3 you have been demoted here as we
now get into our first game on orbital shipyard they're so s and hero now loading up and getting
good to go you predicted uh who did you predict to hero okay oh okay yeah we're odds we're odd
to my friend i have to go with ss let's get into it first game in this best of five in this
second semi-final of the day to see who moves on to the grand final between hero and sos they
face off against one another again and to the bottom left-hand corner we have our red
protest representing cj-entus it is of course hero three times until extreme master's champion
looking to repeat here once again and then up to the top right we have our blue
protest representing jenna green wings it is s os i'm so excited man this is their first encounter
in legacy of the void actually they've met eight times in the past four of those times were last
year in 2015 and actually back then he was sos that won three out of those four times so uh
cannot wait to see here if hero can finally try to even the score here a little bit more because
it's uh man that that's one hundred thousand dollars final i'm pretty sure he's still as
he's on his vine yeah i mean despite them like having those win ratios against one another or whatever
i think that one's the one that stings the most down everything and actually even build otherwise
hero right now is the one going for the wall of i predicted it would be ss that would go for
something like this but nope hero wants to try and get uh one of this himself here and almost as
if ss new he sneaked a probe in before he was sealed up so he's scattered early enough to make sure
he was gonna be in there and ss being the guy who usually plays with this kind of build quite a
bit himself right now he must be he must be so happy he's on cloud nine man he's like well i've
used this time so many times for myself i know exactly what i need to look out for right now and i
mean i mean just great position for sure on this probe you know it's funny because it might actually
get through these shields and do a small little bit damage to that pile on we'll see in a moment
uh because it's not being a thing being built just yet he'll get his mother should call on the
way very soon along with an adapt the adapt normally gonna be sent out of the probe but actually
he's rallied it round to the back and the probe is abandoned not location and even from the down
of pylon to block this is great like i think he realized there was gonna be a quick next
associate from here also and also like these forces the adept to either go inside of the main
of hero and be trapped there or be sent outside like look at the gateway if he sends that outside
the adept won't be killing the one be killing the pylon if he sends it inside he's trapped inside
so already he's so good his his own point whoa uh oh triple pylon hero in the main base
this is not gonna do anything i think sos is gonna have his own overcharges i'm not sure why he's
not overcharging here just yet maybe he's afraid i hear we're just canceling remake the pylon
elsewhere and actually here oh my god he's making more and more pylons sos is gonna have to use
the overcharge really soon here because the adept is on us there as well yeah there are three
upon pylons sos plays down while all of these were being added on just so that you can get that
defense going if he needs to the mothership court is still not there you though and this was quite
the investment for hero because his next this was blocked by comb i mean what else is he gonna do
with the minerals it's not a unit to kill it so he couldn't expand sos not overcharging yet he's
gonna do that now not hero able to get one of those off he's gonna go for the probes and he gets
quite a few already oh my god five before he got down naturally denying a lot of mining time as
well there we pull that out for a moment see a hero kind of moving forwards with that and he has
one probe slowly working away at the panel on the back that was well worth it here 24 probes for
a hero 21 for sos is he gonna let that finish no just gonna cancel the shade and that pylon on
the natural man he's like taking forever to eventually remove this here yeah adept's gonna send
sionic transfer and shade intowards the main base away from those stalkers and they will actually go
in there but they walk straight into the oracle as well as another chicor that with the photo
on our charge hero is in the driver seat here and the the great thing about this too is that like
with these leads he's gonna be playing very aggressive he's getting you gateway across the map to be
able to walk in very quickly he's on stagatek he's getting finixes and that oracle of sos i'm really
worried for it if he flies into a pinix and he's gonna do just that as well oh they need to
stalk especially help it out stalkers of sos of euro sorry i actually trapped out of his base here but
i think it's it's the end of the world because he's getting finixes behind and being ahead in
finix versus phoenix he's gonna be great here for him two stalkers versus the oracle there and in
terms of trade and then picking up another stalker picking up another one and that will be guaranteed
kills off here once again for hero who putting on this aggression so early on against sos it's like
the roles of reverse from how their series of work in the previous situation of the game and sos
behind this didn't use his stagate for anything he's going for double additional gateway twilight council
he has no pylon at the ramp so now hero is gonna proxy his own pylons there is already one centry though
if sos manages to get more he's gonna need a lot of pylons though yeah this ramp and that
probe is being chased on this is super important i mean if he wants to get in himself yet the
pylons they're from to warp him but it doesn't even need to cancel it to let them in he can just
kill this part probe on pylon off and the all the centry goes down as well so the force you'll
blocks out for a moment but it's not long enough all hero has a massive army in comparison sos has
nothing here he's got one stalker and one more to ship go through his name i think you might just die
i think so there goes some other ship core he's gonna be out take down a few of these stalkers as well
gg hero takes game at number one after an aggressive pylon opener until the sport and overcharges
the rules have been reversed kelo is indeed as this man here on your screen this time around
is he's the angry one almost it's almost as if he's the angry one he's like
last time you want to attack you you're the one doing damage youtube all my money
three bench time i almost wanted to say hero here against sos he's like i am taking no bs this is mine
i am just gonna bring the fight to you in comparison to what we actually had in previous series and
wow well what a way to start it off hero taking that first game and the thing is is the
for sos it's such an awkward position to be after the pylons have done damage after the
cause you disruption you know you're blocking off your opponent's natural but then once that pylons
gone behind it what's he doing is he doing the follow up can you really see in his main base
it's difficult to me it's really weird because i really felt like sos was in a great position
he scouted was what he was up against he blocked his opponent's nexus almost indefinitely because hero
was going on the aggression so if sos had used his own overcharge earlier by the time the
modorship core of hero would have reached across the map they wouldn't have been any pylon to
overcharge but now he waited way too long to use his own overcharge so he started losing probes
and when you lose six probes early on in a pvp like this you know already that it's gonna be
a really tough game for you to win because you start very far behind in economy so that's exactly
what happened here and sos i think maybe he misread the timing a little bit that which the
modorship core of his opponent was gonna arrive all right well we're loading up onto pran
terraces here for our second game between hero and sos and mpvp i mean is there really wild deviations
for this map to people go for golds early is that difficult is that gonna be a factor at all
usually no you don't really go for gold very quickly especially like even going for nexus he's a
big part of the meta but Koreans do it a lot less going for a very quick nexus because it seems
like they play sore aggressive sieve and so well over there that they'd be able to kill somebody who
tried to go for that so we'll see all right up to the top left then one game up currently in this
best of five representing cj enters it is hero looking good in that first game really bringing it
and looking good period not entirely expected there from sos and then down to the bottom right
we have our blue pro toss representing generic green wins it is s os with a pile on it is natural ramp
yeah he's gonna be playing a little bit of a trickier call here himself with probably some
some aggression like when you get a gateway like this usually you're gonna want to play a
aggressive what is it gonna be the way exactly is he gonna go for the full wall you think that like
yeah i have four there is like two main reasons why we'll put a gateway here number one he wants to
reach his opponent space earlier than if he had a gateway in his main number two he might want to
wall of entirely and then going to either something like a nexus or dt's and for his opponents it
will be almost impossible to scout because they you will need a flying unit and it's only the
money ship call that you can get that fast that can see whether or not there is an exit so it can
be very tricky to play against this kind of style and he's actually gonna be a nexus here for sos
but a probe trying to get up here if this is completely fully walled off he won't really
completely know that's the case i guess can you read into the cybernet is call timing though
not really i think no okay it did no no no not really it was started like very shortly after the
gateway would have been about the same if the simulator had been made instead of of nexus and
yeah he wanted to go for some kind of one base so now hero is gonna be in this situation where
he doesn't know if there is an access which is everything if you're facing if you think you're
facing on one base you need to get stalker south you need to get a robo maybe for observer some kind
of detection in case it's dt's if you're facing a nexus you need to expand yourself he could maybe
even take the gold if he somehow realize that there is an access but hero is not gonna be able to know
so now sos is the one in the driver's seat he's the one setting up the pace and i think hero might
just try to be aggressive here because of this yeah fucking like it two stalkers already rally
down all woods haha to fight him in so funny he just makes a fight on his leg hey i'm for real
i'm for real pay attention to me you can't be aggressive my modorship called who almost
almost be reaching your base and hero actually pulls back with his stalkers he pulls back to kill
the pattern he's made oh my god well how can you not respect this like you can know yeah sos is
such a master that's so sick and meanwhile behind it he's just gonna get himself a nice economical
advantage is on top of these pylons too yeah what's your cause coming along i think pylon's so
important yeah by now hero is probably starting to realize what's happening here overcharge gonna be
used yeah trying to work on this pylon but the one at the back was so instrumental in making sure
that these two buildings did not get under power because if they did then that could be a
absolute disaster here for sos he's gonna check the main here will hero he wants to know exactly
what is up against if there is any kind of tech all he's gonna see is double additional gateway
he's gonna know that there is an exus that's already finished on his open a snatch all so he's
gonna go for the all-out aggression here she's might going on everywhere once again and actually
he shot his own stalker there i think for a moment loses one of them modorship core getting pressured
back by stalkers this is just not working here so far from hero is he's done some damage he's
traded but it's not really crippling damage that you need to be doing against this kind of tech and now
sos is gonna start on warping in units three by three he's got two base saturation with more probes
hero as the the robot that just finished and he gets an observer so he's he's still afraid that
there could be some kind of dt's which is a little bit surprising so he's missing in the situation
a little bit he needs to hold us off over and over making sure nothing's gonna get him
I know oh my god pylon going down in the back of the base here for sos this game
what do you expect from hero versus sos though really i'm gonna see the next just as well
yeah oh sos the zero check is the inner side of his main and now though because i think there's
something being walked in there and i'd have to try and snipe some probes where is the modorship core
just walks in blissfully nothing to deny at all does the ship go to the map so there's not
gonna be any overcharge and stalkers they take some time to kill on the depth so that was gonna
get a few stipes yeah in total we have two workers killed again six and he will find this pylon
eventually and so that's 27 probes against 22 and he's got the earlier nexus now all sos has to do
having spotted these opponents second nexus he's to corner boost out probes go for blink and down
the line he can go into disruptor if he wants to and he really feels like hero knows that he has to
try something special the other come back in this game so he's gonna start a warp resume in the
robo bay maybe for some kind of disruptor drop with warp resume speed later maybe the observer's
gonna come in for heroes while to have a look around nexus base he'll see the robo facility only
just halfway complete in the back and then also man the looping round towards the natural sea
that the twilight council is down and upgrading so it would spot that blink being researched
you think that's with going blink against somebody like a warp resume and I think what is gonna be
a disruptor here it would be good for sos but blink takes a very long time to complete so there's a
chance this this ruptur hits before this is ready but being able to spot it here oh my this is
gonna be everything even like he even sees the robo bay researching something like sos right now he's
gonna know exactly what is gonna be up against and then all he has to do now he stasks his units to
defend one of his bases and modus you've got to defend the other one and he's if he doesn't take
any damage he's just gonna keep his lead very nicely here doing really well so far I mean it's
been a cool little start to this game as well to just make sure that the wall up would hold worker-wise
forty one to thirty two so massive economy advantage here for sos and is he actually going to go
on tape a school base or is he going as elsewhere yeah I think both layers are gonna be taking that
third base as so I saw really started his pretty early we saw him already do something similar to
this with a fairly quick third against semis that was even faster than this black when blink is quite
a few seconds away from finishing I think his modus him caught two different bases he's got two
pilots very well placed actually this could die very quickly and he's chased away instantly shut
on the arrestment here double foot and overcharge now it doesn't last as long but I mean it's very
very powerful the blink now on the way all right I should say it lasts a little bit longer but
anyway this is so this is going to blink at the last second and get the warper's him here potentially
he's gonna chase it down does he have a blink soon enough okay still spack but no way with the
warper's him speed very difficult to actually chase that down but now sos is gonna have so much
initiative because he has a blink he can just move out be aggressive and I think he might just
attack actually when you know that your opponent is on low disruptor count you can attack with the
motos and blink stalkers make sure you dodge those those balls and try and finish the game it's
three disruptors though it's gonna be tough but I mean sos he's got a good amount of stalkers
the control needs to be there tries to blink some of those away first misses second one will it
hit anything this is a very long cooldown on these detonations he uses all three hero you shouldn't
have done that now he's gonna be even harder to hold this attack he's got a couple of pylons here
that will help they're not active at all completely dead weight phone over charge gonna go down on
one piling as a bit more energy especially by some time and sos doesn't actually have to commit
because behind this he's getting a warper's him he's getting a dodge when he could drop some
dt's and he's applying so much pressure than hero he's not gonna be getting additional observers he's
just gonna have the one down there blink's way one the only one of the two balls actually hits that
it multiple is gonna come in as well because separates off some of those units oh actually lose
two of the centuries there to that disruptor but the warper's him is on its way there is one single
observer here for sos so if there is some kind of dt drop in the natural and main very quickly plus
a dt walking to the third base at the same time that could be a lot of probes that die here
hey we're just looking to use these f- shades as a scouting mechanism doesn't really see
anything they've already moved back as they are me here of sos actually like you can remove the
dt's with some good uh disrupted detonation but against like a very good player usually is just
gonna move back dodge these and our dt's are being wiped in they're gonna be dropped in the main looks
like it's gonna be the two of them and even a third that's for the third base I think
and usually oh no he loads it up well no no okay being cheeky fell up the fight gonna go down
he gets himself under structure nice to blink away from there there's two immortals do cause
some problems he actually spots the spot he's not ready coming in he's not ready you're here
as one observer that's on the map right now he's gonna have to walk all the way back and he's
in so much trouble that's gonna be what 20 probes dead maybe oh oh he gets the first dt wow
i did not expect that and the dt in the third base as well was killing some probes that's already
nine probes here oh so much damage been done oh sacrifice is the stalker for it but i mean to
alleviate some of the pressure but another ten plus gonna be warped into the main base and this
is really causing heroes so many problems sos in the meantime being active with the stalkers as
well trying to find some room to do some damage he's saturated on three bases himself now he's
walking leads he's gonna be massive actually no it's just 59 to 53 so i think that's a lot of
it's out there eventually but oh there we go and more more stalkers just gonna get warped
ten second robot actually from sos so he might be slowing down this game a little bit more hero
it looks like he might want to go into blink himself because he's getting a twilight council i don't
think he wants to go for charge here because when you're facing disruptor yourself it's gonna be
really hard to win if you go for a ground army still more dark ten plus just being dropped off
all the time here by sos there's no blink there's no blink for hero i can't shut this down properly
ah it's difficult especially with how quickly warpersons are able to actually pick up units from
further away fourth base is on the way warpers actually does spot that there so he's gonna warpin
quite a few adept to put some harass on but he could get the robot so to the front here that'd be big
and it's gonna get an easy snipe pound wow that's the mana robo yeah the one that you made too far
out that gets sniped oh oh geez these warpers are there to be so careful i mean here are kind of
fought to lose warper he needs to keep the pressure on himself to make sure that he can alleviate
from the other side of the map oh that's surprising i think hero realizes that once again he's behind
in this game so instead of trying to take the the natural fault base that you would take which is
the other goal he takes this one solo for the like hidden base which could end up being spotted here
right by sos but like having double disruptor production against your opponent who's only on one
robo because he sniped it this is just great for sos here clearly try to stop the disruptor
as once again we'll do those are models in tandem are very very powerful sos gonna be playing
aggressive here i think in a minute he's gonna be moving out trying to get some good disruptor
shots he's gonna be safe on his four bases with the cannon state is getting in static defense now
what person is with this army wow but this is very dangerous okay don't want to get that
blink tundra all he needs to keep our warpers in life it needs to do something and still
another warper's him up towards the top or even the original warper's and try and do something
catches a few of those stalkers there with the initial disruptor shot
not quite able to kill the warper's him here and uh properly shut it down
blink finally starts for hero well better than ever yeah good to have to do something i'm actually
really surprised that sos didn't try to play more aggressive but i guess he was behind on the disruptor
count and he realized that bit but still i i think i can somebody who doesn't have blink you
have so much room to attack and get some big detonations i'm gonna move across here with this
strong strong army he has at the moment disruptor doesn't catch a damn thing where the disruptors
okay so there's four of them in the back here the supplies actually considering how this game has
gone here was done a fantastic job of staying alive and somehow stabilizing he's ahead in walkers
if he doesn't die here and like staying this game longer he might have a shot i really thought like
sos would find a way to attack here sometime soon and you know sealed the deal still one dancer i'm
bouncing back against this i mean another disruptor wall is gonna come out but it's not gonna connect
with sos is small poke forwards as long as sos can trade out without having blink he can trade
stalker for stalker and then just get away what's that up there oh yeah and observe it okay it's
flooding the prison keeping an eye out whoop that disruptor yeah you can't blink forward that's
the thing though i see over here because if you do then and more disruptors come in with some big
detonations actually that's right to come out of the time very very nice few more stalkers go down
all of these trades definitely going in favor of sos he's just controlling better blink not done yet
so important together now eventually does get it though hero it's just so hard to attack against
disruptors and sos i think he's found a way here to try and do some damage maybe try and pull
his opponent out of position he's got no supply spurs that's force base as well which is very
important yeah the disruptors were exchanging blows into the middle but those allies did cause some
problems of a charge so sick it's really good that was like like 12 zealots yeah they just melted
it's so powerful but oh well and at least you can't get a million of them at the same time i
guess i remember which game was it casting it was like eight pylons floating over charged before
patch it's crazy for a defense but i'm gonna see that these stalkers just wrapping around and
looking for some alternate paths to pawn some aggression themselves and they've done a good job
they can get out of here they have blink up cooldown sos now with the fifth base i can't believe
this game as a we actually might see a really long game here between these two there they're so
evenly matched here and as i say that's disruptor force going in everywhere and he split up so much
of his army he's actually gonna blink it aggressively against this just from force go in and catch a
lot of those stalkers look at the supplies and they're also combating these guys so i'm sorry
i didn't supply what uh hero sorry sos might have overextended here with this attack even though
he traded pretty well and his army is looking really scary what's going on here i mean the one
thing that's going in sos is favor is the fact that eventually he will have more bases than his opponent
but that was crazy engagement hero got the far better end of those trades in the end look at
this surprising army and walk it there so even as well this this is crazy game here we are seeing
on map number two yeah stalker's just gonna press up against this it does have plus two but also
blackwise plus two is done for hero two disruptors in there so he's got to be careful about how we
orchestrate this attack wow sos known five bases and no-tampest prospect here so far for either
player two dt's are being warped in i think in the main this could be a great move for sos here there
is only once you can do zero time but there's an observer anyway hero with the four side here
most of course will be able to deal with that as well but still more units getting warped in there
few more zealots now all with that cannon almost down phone overcharge about to dissipate as well
who I've seen on time actually oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh blinks out of that but he
loses himself disruptors as well as a stalker or two but now this is where sos really wraps it up
he's got a huge army advantage here after being able to have all of those bases at the back of this
going for it was instead blinking forwards he knows there's no disruptors there and he's gonna
try and come in for the defense what is it so many disruptors in the process here is hero he is
being dismantled and he'll have to back on out from here because sos army was all together i
decided to get in there very very seriously to force an overextension here for hero to tell hero
you need to come in right now and try and defend this because otherwise i'm gonna kill you
entire army and then that's when you get these big detonations that your forcing mistakes are out
of your opponent his army has to come in hot and those disruptors tied that start dying from
your opponent's disruptors hero starts a dark trine but he's gonna lose his rubber band gg gave
number two goes to sos he ties it up and wow water game to tie it up and that was there's
some great little engagement towards the end i thought that hero was actually gonna find a great
way back in after the stalk has been separated up didn't quite get the disruptors trades he wanted
off in the middle but in the end sos had so much money well he always has so much money
don't make that joke when heroes are on uh he's actually heroes stayed alive in this game much
longer than i feel anybody else could have yeah he was crazy like with all the damage he was taking
somehow he was finding a way you know to be consistent enough with the pro production and with
everything the micro to positioning to really stain it he was really that last big attack
that sealed the deal here for sos and i feel like he could have made that happen a little bit earlier
sos definitely slowed down a little bit too much at some stages here again but in in the end
solid enough to close it out and uh that's he's just so hot to manage that situation that we saw
here where hero's army was split he just had his stalkers at that north base and the rest of his
army was towards his goal base that was below and then the like i said like sos got in there very
furiously fast and furiously and then hero had to react by sending in his own disruptors very
quickly to try and get some detonations but obviously sos knew that was gonna be the case so he
prepared his own disruptors and then blew up the entire army of hero so a really good move here
by sos to finish things uh on prime terraces we're gonna be going on to just towers for our third game
here who also and what take did they go for that's the big questions here does sos send his probe over
the super fast and try and get and make sure he's gonna be a past uh because well i mean he tried
to be in that first game uh but then he just kind of had pylons all up in his face and uh it wasn't
the happiest of time do we see a nexus first against a proxy gate
to all of this that's the crazy thing about like you see the void man i mean like
the the build in p the stiring builds in pvp uh like you can have so much variance compared to where
we were and say like hardest well actually i would say hard this one kind of got a bit more varied
like towards the end for sure but i actually think it it would be so crazy if ss was to go for a proxy
it's like hey let's give him a little flashback you know like from that one tournament we played
in the grand finals i think hero if you saw even if he scouted proxy gateways you probably like
we'll skip a few hot bits and panicked a little bit in his mind we'll see what these two choose to
go for after two very intensive uh decision making games here number one and two ss is uh is such a master
really or like this build orders and everything always seems to know exactly when he needs to go for
didn't quite find too much success in map number one because it might actually like if you think
about it when ss is the one like properly attacking and when he gets to build all the right he doesn't
really doesn't really lose whereas last game he started the nexus and then he puts doubts in hero
said hero didn't really know what to do he didn't really know what he was facing so he is the one
who went for the attack but he was already provoked by ss so ss was just able to be like okay well
you're going for the attack this time i didn't defend well enough the first time this time around
i'm gonna use my overcharge on time i'm gonna get enough units to make sure i don't take any damage
yeah from there he was always in a good position sure hero stayed alive and did uh he took every
single steps properly to make sure he was gonna have a fighting chance down the line but ss was just
solid the whole way with everything macro take wise upgrades he started his bases some time
every single time that he needed to take them and that was a very impressive game out of him i think
altogether you know a lot of people they look at this guy and maybe you know they're not particularly
familiar with stock up that i go yeah another one of those portals who love to play cheesy and
throwing crazy builds sure but this guy is some of the best macro that you can see in stock up too
i think as well yeah fantastic stuff and again these games really aren't disappointing today at all
even the even the three one that we had before you know as much as the score line was as much as
he could have been a three two he was the series that we definitely would have hoped for i think
yeah oh yeah for sure for sure these have been some really good games so far um we have just had
to disconnect from our host in the lobby here which is why it's taking a little bit longer to get
into our third game which is looking to be rectified here by our admins in just a moment
to get into game number three as hero and ss stare each other down through the walls that they
can't really see each other just yet i wonder if uh john actually has a preference between these two
and you know what i'm looking at him right now and he's playing ladder so probably not
no i guess not
john does it have a care in the world
bion is so good actually like honestly like it feels like
whoever of ss and hero that's going up against bion on paper there might be the heavy favorite
you know because of like their past earnings and all that but i really feel like
bion shouldn't be worried about either of them like as long as he plays really well
he's he's gonna have a chance against either he's actually had pretty unreal results
lately i think it's um bion you mean yeah yeah i think it's um
holy moly on twitter that posted like a screenshot of like uh all the tournaments
he's been in uh in in finals of the holy moly it's like an insane amount i think he's like what
over ten maybe uh oh a lot a lot of games really clean let's get into this game hero is not
producing probes up to the top left-hand corner we have our red pro toss it will be cjns as
is hero and down to the bottom left we have our blue pro toss it is jina green wings s os
tying up the series and that is a fast fast gateway to start things off here from hero
yeah and with the wall of as well which both players are going for so apparently wall of
sargood in pvp and uh everybody should use them yeah especially on these pocket they actually if
you think about it in the first two maps whoever went for a wall of one the game even though obviously
yeah he was very specific bills and stuff and they could have gone either way it definitely worked out
in the end and before like pvp's like the new pvp's like you wall of except you don't even leave a hole
like you properly wall of everything exactly full full wall of they think the terrans you can't move
those pylons guys you can have to kill them and that etc but he guess a proven now already just
that's what seems like wait a minute i get it was pretty quick overall so he did sacrifice a
little bit of economy for this did hero yeah and here at this time actually won't even completely
out perfect wall because the probes already and i think you realize is that he fee walls off
completely he might find himself in the same position that we saw him in map number one where he's
a pylon going up on his natural he can't start the nexus and he can't let the units be uh
walked in inside of his main because then he would be trapped there yeah not the best of spots to
be him this uh what road from here is gonna get over that sos being able to be the one that uh
wins for the wall of here it's actually again gonna be a great achievement here because he
is not gonna know where he's facing he's not gonna know whether or not there's the next he sees
the double gateway though and he's gonna see the double at that production but the question behind
this is always is there an access is there a stargate is there dt's you can never know and sometimes
they can even be blink with like a proxy pylon the proxy gateway to whopping quickly and some kind
of three or four gate blink and it will be stargate as the response here from sos so like of course
we're in sir we haven't seen him uh play with the stargate uh properly so far yeah we we saw a little
bit of fits earlier in map number one but back then he was sos that uh he was hero that run uh
that run the show and at one uh throws down a pylon here but it spotted very very quickly by sos
along with the pro uh the adept being able to kill off the probe as well so that's a good start
by sos to just get full information on what's going on it's gonna be stargate as well for hero
but he starts it vastly uh slower than sos which could be really bad now the question is do we see
a noracle or phoenix here being made by sos and it's a noracle so if hero manages to overcharge his
pylon sometime back at home when uh the oracles gonna hit and then behind this gets phoenixes
he could be okay but right now hero is across the map with his mulletier part he's gonna check
the stargate then recall full wall off from the hero very quickly because of those shades that
wanted to get in oh did you see the stargate did he not did he not get the stargate he's going to
run back he's gonna see it now yeah he has to so he's gonna overcharge oh dude he's no overcharge
left for his choice now he's just got one but i don't think he can use it anymore what came out
with it was the oracle right okay so let's get a head on the way over to the side the adeptus
still working away at that pylon i'm afraid that the oracles gonna try to fly in there because
in this case sos has no info so he's actually gonna fly into a phoenix potentially
yeah because he couldn't get in at all with the adeptus now they've killed this often they could
technically send a shade in but by the time they get in it's all too late there's the phoenix
there's the phone overcharge and the oracle will be denied and the adeptus will be killed as well
only oh he killed three probes which is not bad but that's i mean when you lose two adeptus and
an oracle usually you expect to kill more like 10 probes not three and second target goes down here
whoa sos all right i think you realize that he's in trouble so he's gonna take the gasses on his
natural very quickly and he's gonna try to come back on the phoenix count here even though he knows
that he just threw an oracle into a phoenix which is obviously really bad wow what a serious man
yeah great games really all very varied to be honest with you this is now gonna end up being
in a complete and dominant air war here if hero isn't careful he's going to the twilight council
yeah you know against this it's difficult i think that's smart actually hero wants to be aggressive
he knows that he's gonna have more phoenixes here for the moments so he's gonna poke at the ramp
try to foster overcharge and then try to use his phoenixes to do some damage here and there
so sick for an overcharge it's so hard trying to get into the walls this mineral line get
himself two probes but now he's in a bit of a tight bind actually with those phoenix they took
some free damage and he's gonna lose one oh one for one okay hero made the twilight by the way
behind this this is gonna be blink all details here blink blink starts blink okay so we should be
seeing additional gateways here going down and him transitioning i mean does he fully read into
the fact that there's two targets right now did he see it he must have done right no he didn't see
the stuff i thought the phoenix have flown over it but not close enough no i like this for us
i think i really like it if you're able to surprise with a good amount of phoenixes
he has so much initiative the thing is he's gonna face being sure but phoenixes is so good in defense
anyway that he doesn't really matter and usually what happens when you play phoenix like this is
that you lock your opponent on a couple basis he's very hard for him to move out and properly
attack but it looks like hero might be planning to attack anywhere because it's proxying a gateway
out on the map to be able to warp in quicker actually i i don't know if it will come to this but i
won't do it first so it's down the line was thinking about playing with mass air on this map you
mass air is so strong because you can take a third base and fourth base so easily six gateways
in total being added on extra here for hero this is and seven going down this is gonna be a big
big attack here and that's trying as well whoa everything man all right and the kitchen sink let's go
everything pylon even going down into wards the natural it wasn't spotted third even i should say
and the phoenix almost for nothing the problem for us is that it doesn't know this is coming so
he's not getting enough pylons to properly defend with the overcharge yeah and he only has two gateways
switch up out by one single autosis pylon oh you're right oh you're not the back of the
back of the back i think he's starting to realize he's not back at home ready to defend though
these stalkers they have a deba to have blink they're gonna blink up your ramp bro oh this is
just gonna be so difficult to hold a he's gonna be able to warp in very very aggressively with all
of this he's out on the map he's trying to catch his uppeners phoenixes here it's not gonna be enough
this is gonna be so bad for him he's gonna lose that pylon at the front he needs another phone
over charge but he barely has the energy to actually get any more after that and the pylon's gonna
die anywhere that's gonna underpower all of this phoenixes are gonna be able to pick up a few of
these stalkers he needs more stalkers here there's hero though to continue this on oh he might
have enough we just the phoenixes the list is a great srs went straight for the his uppeners phoenix
killed them all but he loses a lot of the damage here from the phoenix when he was in the pit of
thankfully he had a lot of energy to keep picking things up he might be able to kill all of this
with phoenix alone with just a little bit of extra firepower on the ground hero might have
attacked a little bit too early here if you waited for one or two more psych psycho weapon but this
is something what in there is no detection there is no robo you need to one of these ramp it's all
there's the force field there's the force field does he see it i think that's what ss
you can even see it it just gets it oh he saw it walking on it
i need to see it's not a robot this is gonna be really tough actually going straight for pro gg
wow i thought ss as seen that shit just everything by the way like if he sees it here
he's wallsoft his ramp force fields gets a no it gets an observer but now like
he was gonna take forever to get an oracle he did not even start one on time so
what crazy series in games that's so crazy that's so crazy i mean the commitment
i totally agree with what you were saying about the stalkers being you thought that there were a
little bit early in terms of the attack maybe a few marks around so maybe there was just a
distraction but that makes it an even bigger gamble yeah exactly that's that's a huge gamble
to hope that your dot temp has just gone over all noticed during all of that but the thing is is that
that's the kind of mind of hero he has backup plans to his his strategies which is the okay i'm
gonna hit you with the stalkers it's very potent yeah but if it doesn't work there are still
dark temp has to follow that up whereas some of the players might just be like okay my stalkers
didn't work gg i'm done i mean guess what the two super aggro games that hero has played very well
in he's won sure he lost and pran teres is playing aggressive as well but yeah he was a lot more
so about the fact that you know he got a little bit of an opportunity with some things ss was
super solid in the defense and he didn't know whether or not there was an exes ss in a bit of
trouble here your predictions not looking that great is it no no i i got the first series dead on
but this one not so much right now i definitely can't get it dead on this time at least as hero
has taken his second map in this best of five but i mean i'm happy to be wrong when it comes to
these kind of wild games that we get to see here that was cool stuff by hero i wasn't really expecting a
full blown eight gate to come out off the back of what was going on i thought that game was just
going to transition into a full air war with ss being in a really good spot yeah i mean like yeah
blink against a double star get finished and then you we would have seen both players take a third
base and then he would have been the question of those ss go go mass air or not which you know
always mentioning on this map can be really good but i guess we'll never find out because hero wanted
to take it before that's any did yeah very cool stuff so ruins of serrace are taught for game at
number four what do you make of it there's gonna be you know a little bit of randomness with
the scouting whether you get it right or not there is also some wall of potential but it's not one
of those maps where you have a pocket expands so if you yeah you can't you basically on this map you
can't perfect wall your ramp because otherwise you're trapped in your main and you can go in your
actual so you should plan on expanding you probably shouldn't do that and usually you do needs
to expand at least one time or do unless you plan on doing on one base but then if you open
on scarcity to your trouble so yeah basically i don't think we're gonna see a perfect wall here and
are we gonna see a quick next is your finally it really seems like right now neither of these guys
particularly want to do it we saw ss go for it early on parenthesis but is it time again for
something like this jumping to game number four over to the right hand side it's our red
protos representing cagent so one game away from another final it is hero i think this would make
his fifth intel extreme master's final if you were to actually it was even counting anymore
i feel like you should have a intel extreme master's patch on his jacket he's a partner at this
point and over to the left hand side we have our c oh jenna agreements protos it is sos
not going for the wall it's hero that goes for it so as much as hero sponsors now by the
intel extreme master's pretty much i think sos walked away from more money than anybody in the
intel extreme master's history it's a lot of money it's a lot of money hero would have made it
ridiculous how much money he would have walked away from the intel extreme master's if he
would have actually taken that 100k regardless of that like in terms of success in the intel extreme
master's like hero is probably one of them if not the most successful player in the in these
tournaments yeah he's won so many he's been to the finals so many times i was gonna say even
across like other games as well oh my god sos i guess a hero who i think might be playing aggressive
here even though he's not fully saturated on the gases yet i think like when you open one
base like this with some sort of a wall on your hand you have to play aggressive unluckyly for him
though he's gonna scout his opponent last yeah that's really really far and it takes a lot of time
that probes using a lot of mining time sos is gonna get the scout off first and he will have the
full read that's the way it's opponent's up to that's really unfortunate for hero if you would have
scouted this like first or even second it's so much easier to react to it because you see it early
enough to exactly decide what you want to go into and we've seen in the past how well he can react
to stuff that is scouted whenever he realizes exactly what he's facing so very very unfortunate
here for hero but does he throw some pylons down to put it fear of god into him so i've already
tried to just put one down in the previous game i'm not gonna do that just yet though this probe now
for hero knows where his opponent is just haven't seen anything yeah robo in the back of his middle line
oh okay so because on this map you have a lot of space around your main base something like a war
prism and a big war pin in the main can be very dangerous so if you look in the main of sos like on
the right hand side if your war prism was to fly in there and war pin a lot of units this could be
really tough to hold especially if they're stalkers and they're shooting from afar on to those
buildings of the open and staying outside of the range of the pylons so this could very well be
what we see here yeah additional gateways went down already so i think hero is gonna go all out here
he's like all right i got unlucky i scotted you last guess what i make my own luck and i'm gonna
transfer that into good fortune this step is gonna fly on in with it's shade i'm trying to do a
little bit more damage already got a probe it's gonna have to get out of there though by some time
before his for psionic transference can get him get a man out there but there was already sos was
scaring out in the middle of the map and then looping around to maybe try and get in there again
this is very important on this car's gonna be denied here for another back at home so right now sos
is not gonna know whether there is an access or not so he has to start assuming here
himself which you never want to be doing if you are known that he's a one base then he can just
make sure he gets enough units gets enough finance to hold it but now since he's chased away he's
not gonna know anytime soon no indeed how many adeps we have three against three four
guys the shade misses the probe oh he did so there's still a chance sos sees this
what prisms already on the way it's very late oh if he imagine he had to walk back here with
the probe and seen those four stalkers walking that would have helped so much but sos though
right now he's getting a third gateway he's getting stalker she's gonna start a robo
pilot probe is gonna go into towards the natural as well and now he knows exactly what is going
on for the most part he knows he has to be buckling down for some kind of aggression with no nexus
there this can get very scary he's gonna elevate her everything inside the main here will hero
how long is going down in the main I think yes so s he kind of knows he's sticking around the
natural do you need counts he's actually eight stalkers for sos four for hero but he's gonna walk
in quite a few more and that's a lot of stalkers as well as he's gonna be able to do it
oh if he gets a power pile on these gonna own to power these gameways as well
he needs to get the one on the other side as well and then he could have the power of the majority of
them stalkers actually have to move on back there from that and picking up some of the units in
range of that photon overcharge drain get them away but attempt tanking some of the damage from
the stalkers but warping him more here one gate down he needs those immortals out quickly does sos
I think he's gonna sense some of this in the natural here maybe will a hero having a war
presume here is massive because he can keep on picking up units as they get they're getting shot
out here oh I want that pile on another pile and gets up for sos on the left hand side so he's
been able to walk in more but as he gets that one up the other one goes down so still another gate
is down here for him yeah the unique counts he's gonna be very important and you know what all
he's actually about to come out this could turn everything here for sos who's already got marshy play
he chooses not to even pull probes he's that confident that he's held it oh he's got a lot of
stalkers and they're quite healthy as well here army counties of in favor technically of sos
that immortal does pop out it's in the fight and a hero doesn't really have that much here this
could be too too very swiftly if sos is able to hold on against it because there is no economy
to fall back onto he's gonna get that war prism as well and that is gonna be the hero dashed
from this game sos ties it up and we go on to game number five wow wow wow our attack ration
does it always win kaira as it seems like even though hero has been the one that's definitely
trying to be setting the pace as much as he can here in this series sos has had some
seriously good defense not just on prime teresis earlier but now on runes of seris and both
there is they are mixing it up so much sos finally again here went for another quick nexus sir
again actually just like in prime teresis maybe he's found his own recipe here for success
be quick nexus and the larylac crest is gonna be the next map this game maybe no quick nexus
no this is this has been this are a great series i'm really really enjoying the two series that
we've had here so far and then god knows what that final has gotten store for us sos oh we know
it's got a store for us it's a pvt well okay all right we we have that bit we have that
bit at least and i'm probably gonna get plushies thrown at me from the analysis desk again so yeah
again great fun all right i put a acupi's himself anyway can i mean he has to know that he's only
merely a host right whoa i don't think he's listening no he's not damn it he's like oh i've got
to hang my vocal chords up there a little bit so no i'm really glad he's not listening right now
but anyway larylac crest will be our map looks like everyone is good to go all right he's still
sticking with what you thought he's still sticking with your prediction your beautiful prediction
yeah i am yeah everybody's definitely good to go right now man everybody is good to go all right well
here robe doing some soul searching here we'd like to defeat sos here and until extreme masters
and he's very close to doing so but his aggression did not work in that previous game
i think we'll see a bit more of a longer drawn out game unless sos bull uh brings us an sos special
unless he gets really aggressive here which he is not afraid to do at all i feel like this series
is the series that we deserve to see back in katavitsi when they've been final like our entertaining
is mean and like our clothes as well and we are finally getting it man they're not for it all right
let's get into it game number five as we are loading on up and getting good to go as we have to
the bottom left hang corner it will be our red protest representative cjentus it is hero
the mandalegions
and then down to the bottom right hang corner it is mr dollar sign dollar sign himself it's sos
yes
with a pylon is main here once again are we gonna see a quick next class out of him again
we want more see the pylon at the ramp here for heroes so
with how aggressive he's been playing he feroz game plan for this entire series was to try and
be aggressive every single game those who mix it up or those who stick to it because
as much as he's been successful twice he's felt twice yeah it's a really really hard
call to make here and it says already gonna scout out in the correct direction with this map being
a two players map he's gonna have to be fortunate as well with this cut but here only on one single
gas so he might be the one going for a single quick next this year whereas sos went for the double
gas and two gateways oh oh so the roles could be reversed rope yeah no blocker reno no blocky block
no one yeah double gas on the other side here for us as you were mentioning it might be time for
sos to go all out on the aggression himself yeah because he's already got the double gateways
setup it's horizontal close position so he's gonna get there very quickly and like I said on this map
I thought he was unlikely that's anybody will go for a quick next because it's so open around
the natural but now this is just ideal for sos he could go into something like adepts
follow the path any kind of attack if you don't go for a target and I recall sure I think he's
gonna be fine anything really let's go pick it scary I mean he knows with the progression of
any nexus that he would take oh cheeky cheeky approaching sticking around
approaching probe hidden pilot tasteless yeah gotta do what you gotta do at this point I mean
it's so it's it's an annoying so genuine annoying to actually catch up in your own nexus here
as sos knowing that it's done there we go and he's gonna stick around here we're gonna have
uh gonna poke on him if you're here or here where you supposed to put down the panels that you're
natural that they're gonna be able to defend the center area he's gonna be almost impossible yeah
it's uh two ramps and then oh gonna spot it oh been spotted you have been outed and he throws
the pilot down right next to it I think heroes reaction has to be additional gateways here down
the line they don't have to get them now because while gate only now started and for sos what
is he gonna be though he's got a probing the main about to make something he's the third gateway so
a lot of stalkers here to try and kill his opponents wow but the initial defense here is there
from hero with his own pilot on you got the probe and the overcharged threats that was hero's probe
uh going down so at least they can't really send over anything else on the other side to be counter
attacks here uh as sos picks that up the stalker's putting away some a little bit of damage over here
but there's no pilot down just yet hero is not going for additional gateways he's getting a robo instead
I think it's a great it could be something like dt's that's the only explanation as he's gonna
see an additional gateway going down here and he probably still can't quite he needs to get
though surely he needs at least one he starts one now and he needs at least one more I think
all right well poking over these stalkers already getting a few good volleys off that's a nice
stop but for an overcharge we'll shoot that away for a moment get some stuff a free pylon up
towards the top at least I really feel PVP is like this weird tower defense game where
pylon counts as pylon of all things pylon wars man yeah
here we were thinking it's all about the nexus wars nope no he's gonna sack the natural I was wondering
about this when I saw the robo and I think he might be a really good choice because second pylon
started too late here to defend for heroes so he's like okay he looks at my like if I try to fight
on my second base I'm gonna die so I'm just gonna sack it look at this and he's he cancelled the
gate where he's warping in a century just to contain knowing what is upon the top two a lock
down is good here but hero already being on the robo and starting in an immortal he could just
get a second immortal maybe and a war prism and then harass I can somebody who wouldn't have
blink because then ss is going into an nexus and there it is sure enough the war prism starts
behind this so ss even though it's gonna be able to go for the lockdown here hero is gonna have
so much initiative here to do something with the war prism and the immortal that he has down the line
wow this is an interesting little dynamic I mean we have seen this in things like heartless one kind
of nexus being taken and these soft contains occurring with these century being irritating but now
let's see how this war prism is gonna fare against the nexus because if he doesn't do good damage
over towards hero on the other side hero ss will gain himself good example of and it's like he's
abandoning the did you see what just happens she moved away from his ramp because he knows that
photon of charge gonna be enough to defend there and he he these units right and then ss looked
up the ramp and he saw you know you know you know it is like wait a second is he already unloading
his units elsewhere it's time to go back but no he wasn't yet so that was a cool bluff here
and ss pull back a little bit too early make sure he was safe at least oh nice pick up that ss
definitely that really takes the wind out of heroes sales I can believe that just up and actually
too far forwards too eager I think he was at home making the nexus and pylon maybe but like that
very characteristic mistake and now there's even an observer following his army here and he's
to get his own to finally kill this yeah his observer's moving over to the other side of the map
to have a look around his opponent's face and all they'll see is gateways and a robo really
once he arrives there so just some of the mortals on the way for either side just the fact that
horizontal close bond like this was always going to be an explosive game yeah especially because
of the bill others they went for as well and now we find ourselves again in a situation where
heroes behind but he's doing a good job of staying in it you know he's on 28 probes against 32 he's
got a similar tech oh he realizes his observer's here and he's trying to get in himself
no we'll not be able to chase that down in the end lost it
Twilight council for both sides now it has been scouted out here by hero on towards the natural
but the hallucinated phoenix they're both gonna go for blink I think the question now is
do they go for disruptor with it or do they try to play aggressive
one thing's for sure though I don't think either player really wants to take massive risks at this
point yeah this is the deciding game in this best of five I feel like they're both gonna scouts
to try and see because they both got centuries by the way they are gonna try to see if the
opponent's going for disruptor and whoever goes for disruptor is gonna be the defensive one
but if you don't see this ruptor then maybe they just stay on bling stalkers which is actually
really weird if you think about it that way I never really thought of that before but if somebody
takes to disruptor is gonna have less to this than you then you can attack yeah force field is
immortal skill him and I have a lot of stalkers blink back and like you so you can properly fight
and like win wind of fight and right now they can't go into disruptors just yet and put till the
point they have the critical mass that allows them to do so you're right it is quite the investment
so you gotta be careful about that the forge is on the way though okay and those plus one weapons
is very important this one the way chronicles works at the moment you can just put it on that forge
and then let it worry about itself really it's already worrying away now on towards hero's forge
I like that hero is going for a much harder upless one and SOS he's gonna go for the double
take down here on the rocks what's up just a dusting I didn't hate your rocks once I hate
twice get out of the way and we'll get access to that third very important robo beth
finally goes down here by the way for hero so I think he's confident enough with his unit counts
to go for this eventually and third base gonna start here from both theirs I mean for immortals
with the potential of locking this position down with centuries he's very very easily defensible
here but for hero so this could be the dream game kaleis the dream game leave the map and go
to the tempest oh that is that is the dream game that's wildly far down the far down the line
and second robo already for hero so even though he's behind on the work account just by little
on the army count just by little he's so confident right now enough to go for an earlier plus one
than his opponent and enough to go for disruptors I guess he knows that if he stays home defensively
he's gonna be alright for the count is a big position actually here I can't believe he just walled
into this location like hero just let him and he's actually going around he's gonna try to
trap him there is nobody to call with this but I don't know if there is enough units for hero to
take a fight just yet probably not he needs to wait for disruptors but surely he's got to do
something himself I mean just letting your first cast go like that yeah he can't oh that's not
the most comfortable spots at all that's when you drop a dark shrine and pray yeah it works
actually yeah if he if any of them were to go for a dark shrine now because there's so many
hallucinations playing around in revealing everything I feel like he will have to be hidden
on the map all right and guardian shield actually went up here for hero anticipating some kind of
fight maybe so it's truly to type G yeah it is and we will have now full wall offs go
oh you can't just walk down here the centuries that are already phone overcharge will push this
away for a moment likewise disruptor I guess the fault panels make this quite a bit harder
yeah potentially work here I'm actually surprised at how bulky SOS is to be so far on the map right
now with this chunk of army that is good more for more yeah best of guardian at turn right
there force field so I'll seal that off for a moment but even just one foot and overcharge is
enough to kind of show him away from that location it's so powerful to disrupt disruptors shots
available for hero this would be a good time to go back home here for SOS and I think it might be
starting to realize it and throw in that extra pylons here is SOS up to the top left so it can
warp in some zealots for aggression if you actually wants to use that later on
they're so even like even those two playwise oh no hero is behind he's got an earlier plus two
both players are going into disruptors on two robo right now and the double gas here on the
third base is going to be saturated later here for hero obviously because of all that happened
earlier SOS is actually scouting a little bit everywhere on the on the map here he's got a bunch
of probes two yeah checking in places very keen to make sure nothing crazy's happening oh that was
two disruptors right yeah oh brilliant a big pick up here yeah it's not a cheap investment at all
two disruptor lead now because of this for heroes so definitely a good thing here finally going
his way I mean of course with his third base delayed for so long it was important that he actually
did get some damage done here and there it's just oh okay so blink out on time got the disruptor
though that was a nice nine pound SOS oh he could get them all or harm shield being activated very
important that the hero very important you got a couple stalkers though because the blink was a
little bit later off a hero SOS is ahead in supply and it looks like he wants to try and close
this the same way he did earlier on prime terraces with a lot of pressure but right now it's not
walking out he still ahead on supply though all he takes is a couple very good detonations and
he's just gonna win the game instantly hero though going for additional gateways right now
and we're gonna be seeing a SOS take an earlier fault base here in a second and the really
cool thing about this is that he's got a pile on the left hand side where a hero could go for a
fault base and if this might for zero to try and go for the middle the six o'clock fault base but
you think his SOS has more supply so it's impossible almost to actually try and get him as
okay he's nothing for these players man I agree it's pretty tough he's just
just keep giving me a heart attack and it's always blinking out so should be okay when behind
Kaira is do the dark shrine dance well there's no dance for the dark shrine you can invent one
it's just invisible you don't see it and it's like oh okay that's your dancing staying there idle
just like at the concert let's uh say the day no man I got crazy I got crazy jumping up and down
but anyway he's sharpters still trying to get their shots off do you know what they can there
there's really not that many cannons actually not that I look at SOS space so did he drop oh
every single time SOS it makes me believe somehow he's gonna blink a little bit too late yeah
it's only for a second you know he doesn't have to wait that long actually to blink no he wants to
attempt the devil exactly he's like wait another trip to come in down trying to go into the
mortals oh good shot hot and shields was not activated in time it's very disappointing that
hero doesn't have a war prison because if you had a one right now he could send in a bunch of
dts across the map drop them in the main of his opponents and do a lot of damage he's warping
in dts somewhere in the natural of SOS okay he's just gonna send him like this where are they oh
okay there's some yeah there's some adepts in a what I want for him as well if he sends them in that
base he shouldn't send them into the third base because there he's a cannon there they can't get
around the rocks I'm sorry it's made us put it them he's pulling but he's it oh he blinked
forward oh this is ruptured okay they weren't in the right range he blinked forwards onto that
and disruptors were there potentially could have got some shots off but was this is Eagle I man
he misses nothing the the observer just moved slightly into the fray plus three weapons on the way
here for SOS and while we on for hero I guess just plus two right yeah yeah he's going quite far
forwards with just a small chunk of his army okay SOS is not gonna make the semi-stake as hero by
the way he's got a war prism already ready has his dark trine finishes so he works if you
were seeing a bunch of dts and drops them this could be a deadly move here our time pause up to the
top here for hero I can believe his four zero to take this base it's yeah it's not the best
of positions so funny like hero scali the less inside he saw double pilot on his hour it's like
all right I'm not even welcome on my side of the map I'm gonna take this aggressive force base
and try to make something happen with some good disruptor shots economies for the moment are
pretty equal by the looks of things SOS just teetering forward slightly because he has that healthy
mining base up to the top and now some stock because I'm gonna kill off the pylon so you can
actually expand over towards their modus shrimp shots come out one disruptor going down another one
will be back priced off yeah there is a modus you've got that base down there so with the double
overcharge on these pylons like this should be an easy defense triple focus on down he's
actually committing to this is hero here and you don't have that much energy if he's in here he's
gonna get sealed in just for a nexus oh this is the same thing that we saw already on prion
trs here hero gets in there and says you're gonna have to come in here for multiple angles very
very quickly gets two of these raptors oh here's the mistakes out of SOS hero is trying to bay him in
his trine I get the all toothed now that I think I saw this is really really scary here for him
but at the same time all of his army is almost trapped in just rubs his gonna try and go for shots
blinks forwards against all of that gets those down or even activates the barrier on some of these
immortals and now he's gonna sacrifice a lot of stockers but he blinks up onto the high ground
with the aid of the observer he might be trying to keep himself done I think he's doing everything
he didn't get the nexus oh okay he needs to get in that that would be really silly he's trapped
he's gonna lose all of this and hero is heading elsewhere with the rest of his army army supplies 70
it's still in favor of SOS but his army so far out of position he has to deal with this if he
got this based I'll be amazing barrier gets activated onto those immortals and more disruptors
shots go off he's got to be so careful though SOS doesn't have anything to buffer his
amount disruptors there at the front and he's actually gonna target the sexist down if he gets this
nexus here hero and the army supplies stay as they do and he does get it look at the mineral
surface who has this falling apart here he's not mackering right now he's not getting a
pilot he's gonna be suplay blocked and right now hero is gonna have his own fourth base this is
insane as SOS right now has to make something happen with this army dark tempals are on the left
hand side actually killing off a few of these units and there's a kind of net to actually deal
with it but he could get on some of the stockers here hero has to hold on against the biggest army
he's gonna face this game heroes coming in from behind with a huge chunk of his army the disruptors
and the immortals more importantly I don't think he has enough he needs to hit some great
detonations here with the with the disruptors he gets the nexus he backs on out he's got his own
nexus on the way behind this yeah that's not a stocker so I think to get a snipe on this so he's
gonna have to get out of there SOS with the double nexus remake and we're gonna be on 38 pro for SOS
43 for hero who starts or I guess we start the fourth base in this time on the left hand side how is
hero gonna buy time it's gonna have to be some a lot of disruptors laying down some siege on towards
those locations but this is a huge army from SOS absolutely yeah it's it's gonna be really tough
oh and he lost the woppers move to the left hand side did it I mean that's a small prize here
for hero 71 armies to play for hero 101 for SOS can he do it somehow he's gonna need some big
detonations but right now SOS is the one with a great position here is the one who could just go
for that for base and get a cancel on it stockers the remaining of the walls stop blinking get
themselves a few pro's build time he's still buying time the entire army's being pulled back he's
learned and he's just wonders oh good bye the structures so how many did you lose this might just
be good life yeah he's he's killed everything like this just killed so much supply this might just
be game this might be a winning movie of for SOS where does he spend is he was so bossy because
if he runs or blink forward he would have sniped all of these disruptors and not lost any
stalkers yeah because that was all of the shot of the disruptors so we took a big gamble once
again and this one might have paid off with the series win here heroes stalkers actually called
themselves one disruptor up the front they're actually all leading with charge here SOS is so if he
would have been super careful about that maybe he could have got more but he doesn't want to take
the chance doesn't want to take the risk he needs to replenish his disruptor count completely
he's got only two against seven this is gonna be so hard for hero to come back against
double observer here being added on for SOS I think he might be starting to realize that hero might
be getting desperate in which case you go for dTs and try to steal the game away from your opponents
SOS does not want to let that happen still stalkers up towards top hero can't afford to lose any of
those really as he needs every unit he can get I'm gonna poke forwards with these stalkers with the
one disruptor back hero is the one we double disruptor production here right now so he's gonna
catch up here in a second he's gonna get two more and he's gonna go up to four against seven here in
a second so somehow hero just doesn't die yeah I don't know how it's possible but it's this is a
great series a fantastic series I'm what a game to finish he offers well down towards the middle
it's a slight trade going off here but it's just blink stalkers the blink stalkers really he sees
the did that attempt line towards the middle there's so much action everywhere all the time this
is crazy like this DT has been doing distance for a very long time in the middle of the map making
sure he kept the vision as much as he could and behind these stalkers on the top right hand side
I still trying to find some room here to harass a little bit but SOS his army is huge though 125
army supply in this oh he actually starts gravity boosters here he's gonna get instructors he needs to
keep those alive he's actually sacrificing some of the stalkers to get one of them yeah it's worth it
you can just use a very few stalkers where's that dark template uh he's gonna ask it whoa
she's flings across but he actually blinks straight into the focus here off SOS and he loses them all
if you're what sent a DT actually in that base there's no detection no cannon as well now he's
gonna come down to this SOS trying to force a big engagement here to try and get some good
detonations oh and the blink is used too late so much damage already being done mod from
the boss gets on the forwards here this is gonna be really really bad for him he almost brought a
good position there to actually just focus down the Nexus but this is a massive army still
here we're trying to stay alive in this but he's running out of disruptor shots and he's running
out of steam here trying to fast SOS is in the driving seat I mean he's got double his opponents
harm supply he's got less workers like if he gives hero any time he could be in trouble but I
don't think he has any plan to do that like in terms of army supply oh yeah there's no holding
this I think the core lifestyle as well there is actually a little bit of those focus to the
purification Nova it's gonna take some of the absolute best disruptor shots here for hero
for him to come back in this game can he do it another one and sending forwards but doesn't really
do anything he's just scared of these disruptor shots but realistically he's got so much the army
supply is massively in favor here of SOS dark Templar on towards this base though he's actually
shutting down some of the economy this is a good detonation I don't think he's got too many left
six against seven he's even dumped numbers I can't believe he even dumped the numbers and taken
down this Nexus as well if he wins this like he's to me is one the tournament this is ridiculous
look he's he's put the economy back in his favor as hero and SOS is not there to attack because he
doesn't know exactly how many disruptors there are so he traded those disruptor shots he lost
on a bit more and he's like okay I got to slow down I got to pull back can he really do that
with one excess less than his opponent and less mining right now SOS is separating up his army a
little bit he needs to get that base knowing that it's very very important right now considering
you lost his Nexus towards DTLAR who knows this more disruptor so the purification Nova once
together the one's gonna come in there from SOS as he has really now smelled blood in the water
that is the perfect opportunity he needs he can see a muscles as well SOS is truly gonna tap
power down this position he loses a few units towards the back but he does not matter he found
the key he needed to unlock this base and SOS here powering on for the victory he just needed
that one connection and he got it in spade that was great stuff there from SOS GG he takes the series
what a beauty pillie to end off this best of five SOS makes it to the finals
my prediction may have been wrong but you know what I don't even care because
Starcraft like this I can watch all day every day Calais that was a crazy series you're really
back and forth even in that last game you know SOS I hadn't supplied in a couple disruptors
detonation it looks a little bit scarier but somehow he found a way in the end to I think it was
really that big detonation of the ramp at the natural that's yeah the way it was like pulling back
I think he realized that hero was probably gonna be knowing that SOS was pulling back and what madman
would leave it disruptors behind yeah send them in alone load up the disruptor shots and
try and land everything on his open and saw me what madman well this man man apparently SOS
three mad scientist madman attation he calculated right once again what a game what a game there
as SOS now moves on into the grand finals he's gonna be facing off against PUN and considering
that two form oh these two players form going into the grand final this is gonna be fantastic I
watching that series there and hero being toppled once again by SOS here I have to think to himself
how do you see beat this guy in these high octane matches but for now guys I believe we have our
interview ready with the man himself it's dollar sign oh dollar sign over at the analysis desk
thank you very much galaris yes we are joined on the desk by SOS and Suzy of course is big
hello pig hello the 12 year Thai pig
uh Suzy first question I want to ask to SOS what what is his thoughts on kind of this rivalry that
him and hero have had over the last couple of years a little library got it's been
now that Junho and I have gone so what do you think about that game game yeah
uh
he thinks it's fate because they're both such good players he's like I know he's a very good player
but so am I and so whenever we're on a tournament anytime we get to the round of four there's
it's fate that we will always play against each other and is it fate that he seems to always win
when it matters how good fate is that he thinks he's a there's luck involved in it he says that
luck probably has followed him through some of this uh okay okay pig all right I mean let's start
off game one to the series overall shipyard um SOS went for a pylon block on here is natural
and then he counter attacked with the big pylon rush can seem to catch SOS by surprise I just
wanted to hear SOS's thoughts on why why did that catch him off guard that first game when
you know the pylon rush was coming up that time was it that time was it that time was it that time
um he feels that actually he knew that the timing of the core hero was going to be faster than him and he was like
well you know even if I try to stop this I don't think I'm going to be able to um and and then he made
a mistake of not making his second pylon as well and so he said that regardless he knew he was going
to lose that as long as he's able to stop it it should have been okay okay but I mean we know how
that went yeah it was a close one though of course I wanted to ask about game two as well then that
was a game where I feel like it got off to a really good start for hero I felt like he had a
anise lead but SOS was just much more commanding in the disruptor battles so I just wanted to ask
your thoughts on what makes you what made you so confident with the disruptor fights then was
that your counter attacks distracting hero what's the secret to your disruptor micro now the second
game is the first time I've been doing well in the first game I think Junho was very well done
but now I think the next game of the game is the game of the game and then I think I think I was going to win
Oh um
okay he says I
controlling a disruptor is not something that a human can do. It's just really hard.
So if you're on the side of avoiding the disruptor, then no matter how fast your hand moves,
you're always going to miss something. And so he felt like if he was on the side of always
constantly dishing that out, he would be on the better end and he feels that he was able to do
better that way. Okay, yeah, pal with the aggression and put the pressure on the opponent.
All right, one last question. Then the final game was absolute madness. I mean, it started off so well for
USOS. You scouted the natural, you saw this very greedy build and you started to punish it, but
hero was very close to bringing it back. So I just want to hear about the emotional rollercoaster
that would have been in that game when you're so close to winning and then hero almost clinches it back.
He said, last game. Oh gosh, that was actually a lot.
He came to a point where he realized that it's better for him to just not expand and just focus on his
what's the word? Distructors? I'm sorry. I knew it in Korean. I was like, he wants to focus on the
disruptors and really play that game and he realized he knew all the situations going into it.
He said that he felt like he knew how things were going to play out. He just needed to focus on
mainly those disruptors and play it out that way. All right, final question. How did he feel when he got
all those 60 disruptors up that ramp? Because just near the end of that game.
I thought it was important because he felt that if he splits it, that he was only facing forward and he was not going to be able to detect that he was coming from a different
angle and so that was very important for him. All right, then final quick question. Then obviously looking forward about the grand finals.
Just kind of an overall question with a couple small ones about Bjorn. Is he worried about Bjorn? There's been a recent patch recently.
How is he feeling? Is he confident? Maybe disadvantage because Bjorn knew that he was going up against a protest no matter what and waiting and ready?
OK.energetic.
Okay.
He's lost a lot to Terran before the patch anyway, so he's like, that doesn't really matter to me anyway.
And?
Because he's good at it, he's good at it.
I think he's going to be able to get a good result.
He thinks Piano is a very good player.
And so if he's able to play to his ability as well, he feels that some really awesome games will be able to unfold before us.
And is he feeling confident that that's going to be a victory or is he a little bit worried?
He said, because I'm playing against Terran, I'm a little worried, yes. But I'm always really good at finals. So in that sense, I'm pretty confident.
All right, thank you very much, Suzy. Thank you very much, SOS.
And that does it for our second match.
And that's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to do my best to win this match.
Suzy, thank you very much, SOS. And that does it for our second semi-final, which leads us to the grand final.
That's just around the corner. Before we go to that, though, do make sure to check out please.tv with the plug-in.
And if you get a highlight into the top 25, you may be on a cell. You'll get your ticket.
Get yourself a ticket to the event in Katowicz, so the World Championship just around the corner.
We're going to take a quick break when we come back. It is time for the grand finals.